<odoo>
    <data>
        <template id="payment_and_delivery_page" name="Payment and delivery Process">
            <t t-call="website.layout">
                <t t-set="additional_title">Payment and delivery Process</t>
                <link rel="stylesheet" href="/mask_cutomization/static/src/scss/payment_and_delivery_page.css"/>
                <t t-set="no_footer" t-value="1"/>
                <t t-call="mask_cutomization.header_banner_xml"/>
                <div class="container">
                    <div class="payment-form-banner">
                        <h4>Delivery and payment methods</h4>
                        <p>You can choose whether your products are delivered to a post office or to your door, and now
                            Posti’s parcel points are also available as an option. If you would like delivery to your
                            door, please provide your telephone number with your order so that Posti can arrange a
                            delivery time. If you wish your products to be delivered to a parcel point, please remember
                            to give your mobile phone number so that you can receive a delivery alert by text message.
                        </p>

                        <p>If you so wish, we are able to deliver gifts directly to the recipient. If you select home
                            delivery as your delivery method, please give the recipient’s telephone number so that Posti
                            can arrange a delivery time.
                        </p>

                        <p>If the products that you order are in stock, the estimated delivery time is 2–5 business
                            days. If a product is temporarily out of stock, we will e-mail you to notify you of the
                            delay.
                        </p>

                        <p>We will deliver your order to your home address. If your order involves customs or other
                            issues concerning local taxes, we will contact you before the order is delivered. Please
                            make sure that your contact details are correct.
                        </p>
                        <h4>Returns</h4>
                        <p>You can inspect the products you have ordered from Aarikka for 14 days after receiving them
                            and decide whether you want to keep them.
                            If the product does not meet your expectations, you can return it or exchange it for another
                            product within 14 days. We require the product to be unused and in its original condition.
                            Products must always be returned in their original packaging.
                        </p>

                        |
                    </div>
                </div>
            </t>
        </template>
    </data>
</odoo>